Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Baroque Works?
I don't know that I've even heard of
such a company Are you sure it exists?
We're just ordinary citizens
of Alabasta, Mr. Marine.
You wouldn't want to hurt good citizens
just because there's a rebellion.
Wait, Sergeant Major, they...
Shut up!
Why were you hesitating, Marine?
If you wait for proof, you
won't prevent anything.
You should be able to tell
who the enemy is immediately.
Yes, we're very sorry, Sergeant.
We only have until 4.30.
We're running out of time.
The clock.
Robot, Robot, Robot.
Hey, listen, Mr.
Seven.
I think this is a very important
mission the boss has assigned to us.
I think you're absolutely correct
about that, Miss Father's Day.
And do you know what else?
I'll bet we'll get big promotions for
pulling this off successfully, Robot, Robot.
I do hope that that is a planned reward.
After all, this is quite a difficult
mission when you think about it,
Miss Father's Day.
We're shooting a cannonball into
the crowd using such a big cannon!
So the reward should be just as big!
Robot, it's almost time
to go now, Mr. Seven!
We're ready to fire!
Yeah!
What is it you're saying?
What is it that you think I
do not understand, Straw Hat?
Kong Kong!
Let me!
I don't think you understand.
You're going to die here very soon.
The poison from my hook
has entered your wound.
Your body is probably
becoming numb right now.
It doesn't matter whether
you win or lose this fight.
Your body will still be buried underneath
the rubble when this temple collapses.
Fifteen seconds until we shoot! Oh!
Cannon aimed at the center of
Palace Square, rivet rivet! Oh!
Fire!
Hey, Nami, what the hell is
it you're trying to do anyway?
We really don't have time to play around!
If we mess this up, we're gonna die!
Hey!
Thanks, Usat, but I already know that!
Now just shut up and stand there quietly!
I'm calculating!
Hey, Nami, shut up if I had
any idea what was going on!
Would you just explain what the
hell it is you're planning already?!
Calm down!
You'll know soon enough!
Are you ready?
Robot, Robot, Robot.
Hey, listen, Mr. Seven.
This is a very special occasion.
I think we should do a countdown.
That's a good plan, Miss Father's Day.
A good plan, a very good plan.
Sounds interesting.
Forecasting a typhoon.
Here we go.
Countdown.
Cyclone Tempo!
What? But wait!
Cyclone Tempo is just
a silly boomerang game
Just head for the clock tower!
What the?
They're flying up?
Chopper!
Jump up to where Sanji is, all right?
Huh? That's it?
This is her big plan?
To make it all the way up
there piggyback like this?
Sanji, you know what to do, right?
We have to hurry!
I think I get the idea, but it's risky.
Well, I guess I just have to do it.
It's too late to turn back at this point.
Tony, let's do this.
Okay, Phoebe, now just hang on tightly.
I see.
That's what they're doing.
Chopper, get on my right leg!
11 seconds!
Here they come!
Good job so far.
So I just throw him to the
top of that tower. Turn!
Yeah, I'm ready.
Come on up.
That's what?
It's a flat of the blade.
Calm down.
It's your footing. Okay.
Nine!
Careful.
There's a couple of weirdos up there.
Yes, I know them.
Oops.
Oh, hello, Miss Wednesday.
Rivet, rivet, rivet.
I'd recognize that little
traitor to our company anywhere.
They noticed!
They did?
We're still in the air.
This is really bad.
If they shoot at us, we're finished.
Whatever it is you really
want can't be in this country.
Aren't I right?
You're fighting for
somebody else's goal now.
And how can there be any
point in time for that?
If only you would just get
rid of a friend or two,
you could easily avoid so many
of these inconvenient problems.
Loyalty is only for idiots and weaklings.
Like I said, you really don't
understand anything, do you?
Vivi...
Vivi is always telling people
not to risk their lives.
She's the first to lay down her
life in order to save others.
If we don't help her,
she'll die. You'll kill her.
You still don't get it.
That's what makes her such a burden.
So why not ditch the
princess and save yourselves?
Because none of us want Vivi to die!
Helping each other is what friends do!
And that's why none of us will leave
her behind or quit fighting you!
As long as she doesn't give up
on her country, neither will we!
Even if that means all the
rest of you end up dead?
If we die, we die.
That's all there is to it.
Adjust Ribbit's Ribbit's Gun for attack!
This is an unexpected catch.
Adjusting Yellow Gun!
How nice, how nice.
This is good.
They are the perfect prey for us.
What do you think you bastards are doing?
Pointing your guns at Phoebe!
This isn't good.
The two of them are a sniper team.
Chopper, I'll throw you guys up anyway.
It'll change the direction, but
you need to figure something out.
Huh? What do I do?
We have seven seconds!
Just figure something out!
Chopper, Phoebe, are you ready?
I'm sending you up.
Ready?
Aim and fire!
Our bullets are set to
crash into each other.
And then they're going to explode!
No!
What an idiot!
He's hit!
Are you ready, baby?
Just throw me with all
your strength, Tony!
It's no use, Robot Robot!
I'm in fire!
Who's that?
Where'd Miss Wednesday go?
Oh, what now?
Peacock! String!
Up there!
You can talk as tough as you want!
And keep blathering on about
friendship if you like?
but your body is still freezing up on you.
You look pathetic, Straw Hat.
Blaster!
Fire!
Is that right?
Right!
Well, princess?
Looks like you missed us!
Rush back!
All right!
Vivi!
Hey!
Out of here, you brats!
Did you sneak in through
the shortcut again?
Gatekeeper! Run!
Would the two of you please say
something to the kids to keep them away?
Hmm? Sure.
Vivi, going somewhere?
The secret phase. Right.
Well, you have a good time.
So, where did Princess Vivi go?
Huh?
Oh, I can't tell you. It's a secret.
The clock tower, huh?
It stopped, right?
Oh, hey.
You're still alive.
Yeah.
What happened with the cannon?
What was that?
What's the matter?
Apparently something's
gone wrong up there.
It's Vivi.
We still haven't seen her.
Oh, no! You guys!
What is it?
The cannonball has a timing device.
If we don't do something, it'll explode!
What did you say?
A time bomb? No.
I was very well prepared, Cobra.
You have to be willing to
admit that much, surely.
The most successful missions always
account for unforeseen circumstances.
In this case, for instance, even if
something happens to the cannoneers,
the cannonball will
still explode on its own.
The attack will only be
delayed by a few seconds or so.
Of course, I did originally want it to
be shot into the center of the square.
But the cannonball is
big enough that it should
do plenty of damage
from right where it is.
Stopping the rebellion.
Saving the kingdom.
All those worthless ideas
you've clung to for so long.
In the end, they just
created more victims for me.
Let me tell you something.
You're never going to save this country.
Dammit, this isn't right!
Stopping the cannoneers should
have stopped the attack!
A timer?
Considering its power, even
if it explodes from up there,
It will still kill all the people
in the square and the town?
Then what's going to happen now?
Oh crap,
does this mean it was impossible all along
for us to stop the
explosion from happening?
He made us spend all
this time looking for it.
He even announced the attack
so we would do just that!
Why?
Just how far will Crocodile insist
on going to make fools of us all?
It's not enough for him to
tear this country apart!
He has to mock us while he's doing it!
Crocodile!
And that's why none of us will leave
her behind or quit fighting you!
As long as she doesn't give up
on her country, neither will we!
You can't
defeat me!
You've finally managed to speak,
and that's all you can come up with.
I suppose it's an acceptable bluff
from a loser who's about to die.
But of course, like any
bluff, it's empty air.
Except I'm the man who'll
be king of the pirates!
Listen up, you damn brat.
If you really knew
anything about this scene,
you wouldn't make such
an idiotic statement.
I told you before, there are
thousands of rookies just like you.
Every one of them chasing
their naive little dreams.
The sooner you understand the
true level of the Grand Line,
the sooner you'll give up
on your foolish dreams!
I'm the one who's gonna beat you.
Wait, was that...
Yeah, I think it's the Birdman.
Pel?
Wow, this place brings
back so many memories.
The Sansan clan's super secret base.
Pel, listen to me.
You certainly were a mischievous
little child, Princess Vivi.
You gave us no end of trouble with
all your pranks and disappearances.
It's Vivi!
What's she doing in the ammunition bunker?
Hey! What happened?
What was that explosion?
Princess Vivi, how many times have we told
you not to go near the ammunition bunker?
You could get hurt!
Al!
Sir!
I was trying to make some
fireworks, but I messed up.
I know it's the anniversary of the
day you joined the army, pal, so?
What are you doing?
I've told you a hundred times.
Never ever come near here!
Just what do you think you're doing?
How dare you touch the princess?
You're through!
No one dares hurt her.
Hold on, Igaram!
It's fine.
It could have been much worse?
What if you were killed?
Faster!
Go higher! Higher!
Vivi, I need you to promise me something.
Never tell the king about this!
He made it clear that I'm
not supposed to do this.
He told me to never go
flying with you on my back.
You're scared, fine, but I'll
never forgive you if you stop.
After all, didn't you say you'd
do anything I wanted you to?
Hey, Hel? Yes?
You train for battle every day Why?
Because I'm a guard It's my
duty to protect this country.
I have to stay strong.
So who will you be fighting?
Who?
I don't know.
But I don't fight.
I protect. They're different?
They serve different purposes.
Hmm.
I don't understand.
I'm so proud that I've been able to
serve you all these years, Princess.
Protecting the Nefertari
family has been an honor.
I am Alabasta's guardian deity.
The Falcon.
And I am sworn to destroy the
enemies of the Royal Family.
I don't know.
Help! Help! Help!
He's gone.
He...saved us all.
This can't be happening!
Stop it!
All of you, are you out of your mind? No!
What the...
Toshiki, I need you to keep a vigilant
eye on this country and where it ends up.
Whether it falls or whether it survives,
The dawn of a brand new and
historic age is on the horizon.
Madness.
Why are they stopping?
Stop fighting! Stop fighting! Please stop!
Stop fighting!
Stop!
Please stop!
Please stop fighting!
Stop fighting!
Stop it, please!
Please stop!
Stop fighting!
Please stop fighting!
Stop!
Stop it!
Please stop fighting!
Please stop!
Stop fighting!
You doped!
Why are you just standing there?
Get your rears in gear!
It doesn't matter how,
just stop the rebellion!
We've got to keep the casualties
as low as we possibly can!
Stop fighting!
Please stop fighting!
The scorpion's poison
should be working by now.
Where does this brat
get his strength from?
Mr.
Five's team was taken down.
Who the hell did it?
Monkey D. Luffy.
Never heard of him.
It must be a mistake.
You're saying that they're still alive?
We've just received word.
Those pirates have arrived.
You're just a two-bit nobody
who comes from who knows where!
You can't beat me!
Do you have any idea who I am?
I don't care who you are
because it doesn't matter!
Whoever you are, I will beat you!
Now fall with this ancient temple
and let the Desert Sands bury you!
Sabers!
Pascados!
Ah!
Ah! Come, come!
Desert!
Star!
Ah! Nooo!
This is the end of the game.
Amazing!
He punched him straight up through
the bedrock beneath the city!
Hey, you guys!
Look there!
Crocodile!
Now that this conflict has escalated,
more blood will be shed
throughout the kingdom.
We're at war.
You're trying to get me home
safely, but there's no time.
I need to get home as quickly as possible.
If I don't make it back in time,
a million innocent citizens will
give their lives needlessly.
Right.
Well, this should be fun.
All we have to do is beat
up that crocodile guy.
Luffy.
I don't know how he got
there in the first place,
but I'm sure it can only mean one thing
I knew it!
I never doubted it for a second!
It can only mean...
Look, he did it! He won!
Please, our enemy is defeated.
Don't shed any more blood.
Stop fighting!
Please stop fighting!
Koza!
Hey, are you alright?
Do you see it?
Don't be so suspicious, Kozan.
The rain will fall.
A battle.
We'll end.
Rain.
The madness has finally stopped.
They're beginning to hesitate.
The rain is starting to clear the air.
Hey!
Are you all right?
Stop fighting!
Listen to me!
They've heard Vivi's voice. Finally.
Phoebe the princess.
Phoebe, I didn't know the
princess had come back.
Sir Crocodile, how did he get here?
What happened to him?
Oh, so they're still
calling him Sir Crocodile.
We'll see if he's Sir
Crocodile after I tell him.
What's what?
Hold on.
Just stay here.
The rain has returned.
And we'll fall again.
As it used to.
Our nightmare is over.
Finally over.
I thank you.
No sweat.